{
    "subject": "resource/WKMG-TV",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Orlando,_Florida",
    "human_readable": "WKMG-TV is located in Orlando, Florida.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9014796614646912,
            "question": "Where is WKMG-TV located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8435699343681335,
            "question": "In what state is WKMG-TV located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7358133792877197,
            "question": "What are some common television channels found in Orlando, Florida?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5719023942947388,
            "question": "Does WKMG-TV operate in a major city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5495473742485046,
            "question": "Are there any notable events that have been covered by WKMG-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.549319326877594,
            "question": "Who owns WKMG-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5358144640922546,
            "question": "Is WKMG-TV a news station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49326184391975403,
            "question": "What type of organization is WKMG-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2986280918121338,
            "question": "How can viewers access WKMG-TV's content online?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2904396057128906,
            "question": "What programming does WKMG-TV offer?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WKMG-TV is located in Orlando, Florida.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5999_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can viewers access WKMG-TV's content online?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5999_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of organization is WKMG-TV?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5999_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is WKMG-TV a news station?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5999_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5999_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5999_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5999_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5999_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5999_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5999_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5999_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5999_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5999_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5999_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that WKMG-TV is a CBS-affiliated television station licensed to Orlando, Florida, United States. Additionally, one of the documents mentions that WKMG's studios are located on John Young Parkway (SR 423) in Orlando, and its transmitter is located in unincorporated Bithlo, Florida, further confirming the location."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently mention that WKMG-TV is located in Orlando, Florida. This supports the statement that WKMG-TV is located in Orlando, Florida."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}